Homemade Mac & Cheese. 70 min · 8 servings · American
Ingredients: 4. 16 oz (1 lb) Tillamook cheese, cubed; 2 cups milk; 3 tablespoons cold butter, cubed; 2 cups uncooked elbow pasta (equals 4 cups cooked)
Step 1. Preheat oven to 350°F and grease a 9x13 baking dish.
Step 2. Cook pasta according to box directions. Drain pasta in a colander when done.
Step 3. Meanwhile, cut cheese and butter into cubes.
Step 4. Layer half of the cooked pasta, cheese, butter, then milk in the baking dish.
Step 5. Repeat with remaining ingredients.
Step 6. Cover with foil and cook for 50–60 min.
Step 7. Uncover the last 10 min to brown the top of the cheese.
You're ready. Use Make It for checkboxes on the page.